Jobs With Justice records 6369
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VII. Publications
  - Jobs With Justice Publications
    - Welfare Reform Confidential Comix, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - "Jobs Justice Joy" Article, 1999-03-22 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Steelabor - A Voice for America's Workforce, Volume 64, 1999-12 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - An Alternative Tashlich, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Jobs with Justice Health Care Action Toolkit, 2000-2003 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Jobs with Justice in Spanish, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Money Made, Workers Forgotten, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Free Trade Area of Americas (FTAA) Quebec 4-Pager, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Jobs with Justice "A Strategic Approach to the New Economy", 2001-02 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - IUE-CWA Electrical Union News, 2001-05-15 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - "Si, Se Puede!" English and Spanish, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2002-05-2002-06 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Assorted Postcards, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Old Publications, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Jobs with Justice Samples, 2004-2005 (Box 27, Folder 48-49)
    - Social Policy - Organizing for Social and Economic Justice, Volume 36, Fall 2005 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Creating Luxury, Enduring Pain - How Hotel Work is Hurting Housekeepers, 2006-04 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Bi-National Perspective on Offshore Outsourcing: A Collaboration Between Indian and U.S. Labor, 2006-10 (Box 27, Folder 38-39)
    - Global Solidarity News, Winter 2008-2009 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Change to Win - From Low Quality to High Prices, CVS is Failing Our Communities, 2008-12 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Department of Professional Employees - Gaming the System, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Economic Meltdown Funnies, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - National Employment Law Project (NELP) - Just Pay, 2009-2010 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Pamphlets, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - CQ Today - The Legislative News - Daily from Congressional Quarterly, 2009-02-03 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Raids on Workers - Destroying Our Rights, 2009-06-18 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Bad Jobs in Goods Movement - Warehouse Work in Will County, Illinois, 2010-2011 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - U.S. Social Forum, Inter-Alliance Dialogue - Enough is Enough! "Basta Ya!", 2010 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Rebuilding America's Communities, 2010-04 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Fair Game - A Strategy Guide for Racial Justice Communications in Obama Era, 2010-05 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Check, Please! - Health and Working Conditions in San Francisco Chinatown Restaurants, 2010-09 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - IPS - America is Not Broke, 2011-11-21 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Good Jobs First - Organizing Transit Riders: A How-To Manual, 2011-12 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Reports and Sessions, 2012 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Tipped Over the Edge - Gender Inequality in the Restaurant Industry, 2012-02-13 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Assorted Pledge Cards, Ballots, ETC, undated (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Martin Luther King Jr. Cards, undated (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - New Jersey Public Worker Advertisement, undated (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Other Publications
    - Labor Notes, 1992-1996 (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
    - Labor Page, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - National Organizers Alliance - The ARK, 1994-2002 (Box 37, Folder 5-6)
    - National Interfaith Committee for Worker Justice - Faith Workers Newsletter, 1996-2000 (Box 37, Folder 7-8)
    - Labor Mailings, 1997-1998 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Labor Notes, 1997-2008 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Welfare Reform - The Jobs Aren't There, 1997-12-10 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Center for Community Change, 1998-1999 (Box 37, Folder 12-13)
    - Center for Community Change - Welfare Reform, 1998-1999 (Box 37, Folder 10-11)
    - Labor Publications, 1999-2002 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Student Organizing, 1999-2008 (Box 37, Folder 15-16)
    - Journal of Southerners on a New Ground, Summer 2000 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - AVODAH: The Jewish Service Corps, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - CCMC: Communications Consortium Media Center, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - CWA News - United We Stand, Volume 61, No. 9, 2001-10 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Modern Healthcare, 2002-07-15 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Global Exchange, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Economic Policy Institute - Briefing Paper, 2003-08 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Labor Press and Reports, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Words that Work: Messaging for Economic Justice, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Irish Congress of Trade Unions, 2006-2008 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Asia Floor Wage, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Transforming Our World: U.S. Grassroots Organizations and Global Justice Movement, 2010 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - United Workers Congress Press, 2010-2014 (Box 37, Folder 26-28)
    - The Movement to End Wage Theft, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - The Nonprofit-Creating Culture: Promising Practices of Successful Movement Networks, Fall/Winter 2013 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Labor Research and Action Network Conference, 2016-06-24-2016-06-25 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - The Employee Free Choice Act Restoring the Right of Workers to Choose Unions - Policy Brief ADA, undated (Box 37, Folder 32)